# KORI ELIAZ

korieliaz@outlook.com
949-220-6397
Linkedin.com/in/korieliaz

Passionate and creative Electrical Engineering undergraduate with demonstrated leadership skills and academic excellence. Eager to bring several years of internship and extracurricular experience to innovate cost-saving exploratory spacecraft system designs. Actively involved in several student outreach programs across the country to promote work in the aerospace industry.

#### SKILLS

- Cameo Systems Modeler
- Requirement Modeling
- Proposal Writing
- C/C++
- MATLAB
- VHDL/Verilog
- Git/CVS
- Linux
- Scrum/Agile
- Rational DOORS
- GUI Design
- Cadence Virtuoso

### EDUCATION

### B.S. Electrical Engineering / Colorado State University - Fort Collins, CO / GPA: 3.978

- Expected Graduation: May 2022
- Honors: Astronaut Scholarship, Tau Beta Pi Scholarship, Outstanding Contribution Award, Dean's List

#### EXPERIENCE

### Systems Engineering Intern - Dragonfly

Lockheed Martin Space - Littleton, CO / Jun 2021 - Present

- Designing the first baseline system model for a deep space exploratory mission in Cameo Systems Modeler
- Collaborating with the NASA and APL customers to compose and verify detailed L3 requirements
- Researching and proposing implementations of new digital technologies to streamline spacecraft production

# Electronics Engineering Intern - Electronically Steered Arrays (ESA) IRAD

Lockheed Martin Space - Littleton, CO / Jun - Aug 2020

- Designed and developed an IP Core to combine three subarray controller chips into one using VHDL
- Crafted unique requirements and interface diagrams for the IP Core Design Requirement Specification
- Saved \$10 million+ for the ESA program through IP Core integration onto various spacecraft

#### Software Engineering Intern - Lucy

Lockheed Martin Space - Littleton, CO / Jun - Aug 2019

- Implemented and tested single fault tolerance flight software for the Lucy spacecraft's thermal module in C
- Wrote 200+ lines of proprietary code/unit tests to ensure spacecraft integrity in case of heater failure
- Modified telecom module to reflect changes in antenna bandwidth and integration with central avionics

#### RESEARCH

# Deputy Principal Investigator - "Space Swiffer" Electrodynamically Repulsive Lunar Dust Brush Aerospace Systems Emulation and Test (ASET) Lab - Fort Collins, CO / Sep 2019 - June 2021

- Leading 5-person team in prototype development of a novel lunar dust mitigation device
- Concept awarded a \$10k NASA research grant for novel design of lunar dust particle repulsion technology

#### EXTRACURRICULARS

## Chapter President / Students for the Exploration and Development of Space / Sep 2020 - Present

- Guiding 30+ CSU students toward fruitful careers in the aerospace industry via self-driven projects
- Fostering innovation by teaching the NASA product development process, proposal writing, quad charts

# Intern Ambassador / Lockheed Martin Space / Aug 2020 - Present

- Producing short videos to promote Lockheed Martin's deep space missions for view by 14k+ followers
- Researching intern roles and responsibilities to increase HR awareness and understanding of intern positions